http://www.bestnet.net/privacy

BestNet Privacy Policy
This policy covers how BestNet treats personal information that BestNet collects and receives, including information related to your past use of BestNet products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable BestNet to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. Our services are designed to give you the information that you want to receive. BestNet will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.
Information on visitorsDuring the course of any visit to BestNet.Net, the pages you see, along with something called a cookie, maybe downloaded to your computer. Most, if not all, websites do this, because cookies allow the website publisher to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the site before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit.
Any information that is supplied by cookies can help us to provide you with a better service and assists us to analyse the profile of our visitors. For example: if on a previous visit you went to, say, the education pages, then we might find this out from your cookie and highlight educational information on a second visit.
What is a cookie?When you enter a site your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie. Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Many sites do this whenever a user visits their site in order to track traffic flows.
Cookies themselves only record those areas of the site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to that user.
Even if you haven't set your computer to reject cookies you can still browse our site anonymously.
Use and storage of your personal informationBestNet does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested.
When you supply any personal information to BestNet.Net we have legal obligations towards you in the way we deal with that data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular webpages that let you know why we are requesting the information) and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else. In general, any information you provide to the BestNet will only be used within the BestNet. It will never be supplied to anyone outside the BestNet without first obtaining your consent, unless we are obliged or permitted by law to disclose it. Also, if you post or send offensive or inappropriate content anywhere on or to BestNet.Net or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on BestNet.Net, and BestNet considers such behaviour to be serious and/or repeated, BestNet can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behaviour. This may include informing relevant third parties such as your ISP, employer, school or e-mail provider about the content and your behaviour.
We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met. For safety reasons, however, BestNet may store messaging transcript data (including message content, names, times and dates) arising from the use of BestNet services. That information will be held only as long as necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely.
Access to your personal informationYou have the right to request a copy of the personal information BestNet holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. (We charge $15 for information requests.) Please address requests to:
Attn: Privacy Policy OfficerBestNet.Net210 N. Tucker Blvd, Suite 700St. Louis, MO 63101USA
Children's PrivacyBestNet.Net is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.
Confidentiality and SecurityWe limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
Your Consent To This AgreementBy using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by BestNet as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Please send any questions about BestNet's Privacy Policy to:
Attn: Privacy Policy OfficerBestNet.Net210 N. Tucker Blvd, Suite 700St. Louis, MO 63101USAFax: 1.314.241.1777
© 1995 - 2014 Bestnet.net. All Rights Reserved.
Telephone: 1.314.621.9991 (24x7), Web: www.Bestnet.net
Powered by
Cybercon.com.
Privacy Policy
Follow Us
